This one's rare. This one's medium-well. Go!
這是三分熟 這是五分熟，快去吧
Hey, Phoebe! How was dinner?!
菲比，晚餐好吃嗎？
Dinner was good! Just saying hi! Now I'm gonna go!
晚餐很好吃，我只是來打招呼 我要走了
-Well, hello there. -Hi.
-你好 -嗨
I didn't see this on the menu.
我在菜單上沒有看到這個
Tim, this is Phoebe. Phoebe, this is Tim, my new sous chef.
提姆，她是菲比 菲比，他是我的新二廚提姆
-So you're Monica's boss? -No, she's my boss.
-你是摩妮卡的老闆 -不，她是我的老闆
-"Sous" is French for "under." -I "sous-stand."
-「二」在法文裡是「之下」的意思 -我「瞭解」了
Tim, I need a calamari and a caesar salad. And could you get me the pesto?
提姆，我要一份烏賊跟一份凱撒沙拉 你可以給我青醬嗎？
-You made pesto? -Yes, I did.
-青醬是你做的？ -沒錯
Would you say your pesto is the best-o?
你覺得你的青醬 是最棒的？
I don't know. I would say it's pretty good-o.
我不知道 我會說它真的很棒
I still need the calamari and salad.
我還是需要烏賊跟沙拉
I like your necklace.
我喜歡你的項鏈
"Coming up, Monica. I have to obey you, otherwise the system breaks down."
「馬上來，摩妮卡，我得服從你 不然的話系統會瓦解」
"l know that." "Then why are we having this conversation? "
「我知道」，「那麼我們為什麼 還要談這些？」
-I made it myself. -You are so talented.
-那是我自己做的 -你真的好有天份
Well, it's no pesto.
那不是青醬
Let's just cut to the chase. You're single. You're single.
我們就別玩遊戲了 你是單身，你也單身
He gets off work at 11. She'll be waiting for your call.
他11點下班 她會等你的電話
I'll give him your number if I could just get one calamari and one caesar salad!
快給我烏賊跟凱撒沙拉 我就會給他你的電話號碼
I did not yell. I am not putting a dollar in the jar.
我沒有大叫 我不必被罰一塊錢
The One With Rachels Date
本集播出：瑞秋的男友
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Wow, Bing! Burning the midnight oil. -You know me, sir.
-賓，你還在熬夜加班 -你很瞭解我的，老闆
Do you know how I can get around the office computer network..
你知道要怎麼避過 辦公室的電腦網路…
so I can access the really good Internet porn?
進去網際網路看 超級精彩的黃色電影嗎？
You're a joker, Bing.
你真愛開玩笑，賓
What's funny about that?
那有什麼好笑的？
-Sorry I kept you waiting so long. -That's okay. Where do you wanna go?
-抱歉讓你等這麼久 -沒關係，你想去哪裡？
I think you know where I wanna go.
我以為你知道我要去哪裡
-The Hard Rock Cafe? -Yeah.
-硬石餐廳？ -對
-Again? -Yeah.
-又要去？ -對
-I'm telling you, I like the food. -You like the Purple Rain display.
-我真的很喜歡那裡的食物 -你喜歡那裡的紫雨展示品
-Hey, Bob. -Hey, Toby. Have a good night.
-嗨，巴伯 -嗨，托比，祝你今晚玩得開心
-Did that guy just call you Toby? -Yeah, he thinks that's my name.
-那傢伙叫你托比？ -對，他以為那是我的名字
-Why don't you correct him? -It's been going on way too long now.
-你為什麼不更正他？ -那是很久以前的事了
The first time, we were just passing each other, so I didn't say anything.
第一次我們錯身而過 所以我什麼都沒說
The next time he said, "Toby, want a doughnut?"
第二次他說 「托比，你要吃甜甜圈嗎？」
I wanted the doughnut.
我想吃甜甜圈
Five years later, the doughnut's gone and I'm still Toby.
五年後甜甜圈早就消化光了 我還是托比
-Chandler, you have to tell him. -That would be so awkward.
-錢德，你得告訴他 -那一定會很可怕
We don't work together. He's on the sixth floor.
我們不在同一個樓層工作 他在六樓
So he calls me Toby once in a while.
他每隔一陣子會叫我托比
It's not like he's calling me Muriel.
反正他不是叫我馬利歐
Muriel. Why would he call you Muriel?
馬利歐 他為什麼要叫你馬利歐？
Oh, my God.
天啊
Chandler "M." Bing.
錢德·M·賓？
It's not just an "M." Your middle name is Muriel!
事實上不是M 你的中間名是馬利歐
It is a family name.
那是家族名字
Chandler Muriel Bing.
錢德·馬利歐·賓
Your parents never even gave you a chance, did they?
你父母真的 不給你任何機會，對吧？
Drake, I've discovered the reason for your memory loss.
德瑞克 我找出你喪失記憶的原因了
What is it?
為什麼？
Your brain transplant wasn't successful.
你的腦部移植手術失敗
Your body's rejecting Jessica's brain.
你的身體排斥潔西卡的腦部
Is it serious?
很嚴重嗎？
Not if we extract tissue from the original body..
如果我們可以從捐贈者的身體 抽取組織…
and synthesize antibodies to stop you from rejecting the brain.
合成抗生素 阻止你排斥移植來的腦部
That sounds simple enough. Let's just do that.
聽起來很簡單 我們就那麼做吧
We would, but when we went to exhume Jessica's body..
我們可以那麼做 但我們想挖出潔西卡的屍體時…
it was gone.
發現它不見了
Very nice, people.
非常不錯，大伙們
I'll change and we can go.
我換了衣服後我們就能離開
-What happened to Jessica's body? -You'll have to see it on TV.
-潔西卡的屍體怎麼了？ -你得看電視才會知道
-You don't know, do you? -Couldn't care less.
-你不知道，對吧？ -我也不在乎
-Good scene, man. -You too.
-你表現的很好 -你也是
What? You weren't in it.
什麼？你根本不是演員
Kash, this is my friend Rachel. Rachel, Kash.
凱許，她是我朋友瑞秋 瑞秋，凱許
-Hi. -Why haven't I seen you here before?
-嗨 -為什麼之前我沒有見過你？
Joey just thinks I'll embarrass him. He thinks I'm a soap opera nut.
喬伊覺得我會丟他的臉 他認為我是肥皂劇迷
Which I'm not. I'm not.
我才不是 真的
Although, I do know your favorite ice cream flavor is butter pecan.
雖然我真的知道 你最喜歡胡桃奶油口味的冰淇淋
And your dog's name is Wally.
你的狗叫做華利
-Look, I'm just stroking your arm. -Here we go.
-天啊，我在摸你的手 -我們走吧
Bye, Kash. Say hi to Wally.
再見，凱許 幫我跟華利問好
-Monica. -Hi.
-摩妮卡 -嗨
I had the best time with Tim last night. He is so sweet.
昨晚我跟提姆玩得很開心 他真的很體貼
I can't wait to get "sous-neath" him.
我等不及 鑽到他的身體下面去
-I have to fire him. -Why?
-我得開除他 -為什麼？
He's terrible. He's slow. He burns things.
他真的很可怕 他的動作超慢，還會把食物燒焦
He lit my pastry chef on fire.
他放火燒我的甜點主廚
He was nervous. You can be intimidating.
他太緊張了 你老是凶巴巴的
And your pastry chef can stand to be taken down a peg.
你的甜點主廚毛髮應該可以少一點
Well, now she has no eyebrows. Mission accomplished.
現在她沒有眉毛 任務完成
But, Monica, he loves his job so much.
但摩妮卡，他熱愛他的工作
Can't you just give him another chance, please?
你不能再給他一次機會嗎？ 拜託
All right. But if he lights someone else on fire, he's gone.
好吧，但如果他再放火燒別人 他非走不可
That's fair. Thank you so much.
那很公平，謝謝你
Looks like he got you a little bit too.
看起來 他也燒到你了
I paid to have this done.
我付錢把頭髮弄成這樣
Love it!
我喜歡
Hey. You know, Kash really liked you.
知道嗎？ 凱許真的喜歡你
He thought you were charming.
他覺得你很迷人
-I thought I was an idiot. -I'm with you.
-我以為我是個白癡 -我贊成
-He asked if you'd go out with him. -I think I'm gonna throw up a little.
-他問你願不願意跟他約會 -我想我得去吐一下
-What did you say? -"No."
-你怎麼說？ -「不」
What?
什麼？
I figured since you're pregnant, you're not gonna be seeing people.
我想因為你懷孕了 你不能跟別人約會
First of all, Kash Ford? Not people.
首先，他是凱許福特 不是一般人
Did you tell him I was pregnant?
你告訴他我懷孕了嗎？
No. I didn't know if you told people. This was when Kash was still "people."
不，我不知道你要不要告訴別人 這時候的凱許是「一般人」
-Good. Just have him call me. -I don't think that's..
-很好，請他打電話給我 -我不覺得…
Go do it or I'll come back to that set. I'll meet more actors.
照我的話做，不然我會回到攝影棚 泡其他的男演員
-Hey, Bob. -How's my pal Toby doing today?
-嘿，巴伯 -我朋友托比今天還好嗎？
If I see him, I'll ask.
我看到他時會幫你問一下
Was that Bob from six you were just talking to?
你剛剛在跟 六樓的巴伯說話？
-Yeah. -You know him?
-對 -你認識他？
We're on a semi-first-name basis.
我們會互叫彼此的名字
-What about adding him to our team? -Bob?
-如果他加入我們的團隊呢？ -巴伯嗎？
Working here with us? Every day? I don't know if he has what it takes.
每天跟我們在這裡一起工作？ 我不知道他有沒有那個能耐
-They love him down on six. -But this is 11.
-六樓的人很喜歡他 -但這裡是11樓
It's almost twice as hard up here.
這裡的工作要難上兩倍
-Okay, Bob will stay put. -I think it's best, sir.
-好吧，巴伯還是不能調職 -我想那麼做是最好的
We do need to find somebody. Work is starting to pile up.
我們真的很缺人 工作開始越積越多了
I've got a stack of documents this high.
我有一疊文件 已經疊到這麼高了
Just toss them in the shredder and claim you never got them.
把它們丟到碎紙機裡 就說你從來沒有收到它們
That's a good one, Bing.
那真的很好笑，賓
What does a guy have to do to be taken seriously around here?
我該怎麼做 他們才會覺得我是認真的？
I gave him another chance, but Tim has got to go.
我再給他一次機會 但提姆非走不可
I called the chef who recommended him to me.
我打電話 給推薦他給我的廚師
He said, "Ha, ha! Gotcha!"
他說「哈，哈，整到你了」
-But don't fire him today. -Why?
-但別在今天開除他 -為什麼？
-Because I'm dumping him today. -You said he was sweet.
-因為今天我要甩掉他 -你說他很體貼
He's too sweet. He calls me all the time.
他太體貼了 他老是打電話給我
"Did you get home okay? Was your shower okay?"
「你平安回家了嗎？ 你的洗澡水夠熱嗎？」
-Don't pick up the phone. -Then he comes over!
-別接電話 -他會親自過來
"I was so worried about you." Be a man!
「我好擔心你」 有點男子氣概吧
So I can't fire him?
所以我不能開除他？
And dump him the same day? He'll kill himself.
讓他在同一天被甩？ 他會自殺的
I'll fire him, and you go out with him another week.
我開除他 你再跟他交往一星期
Are you kidding? Another week with that simp, I'll kill myself.
你在開玩笑嗎？ 再跟他交往一個星期，我會自殺的
We'll both do it today and he'll just have to deal with it.
我們都在今天跟他攤牌 他得自己想辦法應付
Okay. But who's gonna go first? Whoever goes second is the bitch.
好吧，但誰要先說呢？ 第二個說的人就是臭女人
-What? -Fire a guy that's just been dumped?
-什麼？ -開除一個剛剛被甩的男人？
Bitch! And dump a guy that's just been fired?
臭女人 甩掉一個剛剛被開除的男人？
Blond bitch!
金髮臭女人
I wanted to do this days ago, so I think I should go first.
我幾天前就想這麼做 所以我想應該讓我先說
All right, that makes sense.
好吧，你說的有理
But screw you! I'm going first!
但去你的，我要先說
-Toby, you got a sec? -Sure. What's up?
-托比，你有空嗎？ -當然，什麼事？
I wanted to get transferred up here, but it's not gonna happen.
我想被調職到這裡來 但我的美夢破滅
Apparently somebody thinks I'm not "11th-floor material."
很明顯地有人認為 我不是「11樓的材料」
Say, who the hell is this Chandler?
錢德到底是誰？
What's the best excuse for why I'm not drinking on this date tonight?
今晚約會時 哪個借口最適合我用來擋酒？
"I'm a recovering alcoholic, " "I'm a Mormon"..
「我正在戒酒」 「我是摩門教徒」…
or "I got so hammered last night I'm still a little drunk"?
或是「我昨晚喝太醉 現在還在宿醉」？
You're not gonna tell him you're pregnant?
你不打算告訴他 你懷孕了？
I don't think so. Books say wait till the third date to tell the guy..
我想還是不要吧，書上說 等到第三次約會再告訴你的對象…
you got something growing in your uterus.
你的勝子裡 有個東西在成長
-Hey. -Hi.
-嘿 -嗨
What do you want to do tonight?
今晚你要做什麼？
There's a powerful Ukrainian film playing. Interested?
有出很棒的烏克蘭電影 你想看嗎？
No. But I'll go see a normal-person movie with you.
不，但我可以陪你 看一般人看的電影
-Rach, you wanna come? -I can't. I've got a date.
-瑞秋，你要一起來嗎？ -不行，我有約會
-A date? -Yeah. Why, is that weird for you?
-約會？ -對，怎麼了？很奇怪嗎？
Why, no. It's the opposite of weird. It's regular.
不，一點都不奇怪 那很正常
It's mundane. It's actually a little dull.
那太普通了 事實上還有點無聊
It's no Ukrainian film.
它不是烏克蘭電影
Earrings!
耳環
-She's got a date? With who? -I set her up with this actor.
-她有約會？對方是誰？ -我撮合她跟一個男演員
-You set her up? -No.
-你幫她牽紅線？ -不
-What were you thinking? -That it was okay..
-你在想什麼？ -那應該沒關係…
because you two haven't dated in five years.
因為你們兩個 已經分手五年了
I'm worried about my baby. Whoever she dates, my baby dates.
我擔心我的寶寶 跟她約會的人也在跟我的寶寶約會
-Where is this "actor" taking them? -Hey! I'm an "actor" too.
-這個「男演員」要帶她們去哪裡？ -嘿，我也是男演員
They're taking the ferry to a place on Staten lsland.
他們要搭渡輪 到史坦頓島玩
My baby's going on a ferry? Do you have any idea how dangerous those are?
我的寶寶要搭渡輪？ 你知道那有多危險嗎？
Aren't we talking about those big boats that go really slow?
我們是在談 那些速度緩慢的大船吧？
Why not just jump out of an airplane or burn each other with matches?
他們為什麼不去跳飛機 或點火柴把彼此燒了？
-Hey, Joey. -Hey, Kash. Ross, this is Kash.
-嘿，喬伊 -凱許，羅斯，他就是凱許
Hey, I hear you're going on a ferry tonight.
我聽說 今晚你們要去搭渡輪
Bit of a daredevil, are we?
我們有點大膽吧？
Do you guys think this is too slutty? Hi, Kash.
這件洋裝是不是太露了？ 嗨，凱許
-Hey, Rachel. You ready to go? -Yeah. See you guys later.
-瑞秋，你準備好了嗎？ -是的，待會見
Have a great time, you guys. And yes, it is too slutty!
祝你們玩的愉快 那件洋裝的確太露了
Hi.
嗨
I'm glad you called. I feel like I'm always calling you.
我很高興你打電話給我 我也覺得自己太黏你了
What's up? Is everything okay with Phoebe?
什麼事？ 菲比沒事吧？
It will be in a minute.
我待會就會沒事
-Tim, you're a really great guy. -That's because I'm with you.
-提姆，你真的很棒 -那是因為我跟你在一起
It's just, I'm in a place in my life right now where..
但我的人生 現在走到了…
So sorry. "This just in."
抱歉，「剛剛有消息傳過來」
It's the restaurant. Monica needs me right away.
是餐廳在呼叫我 摩妮卡要我馬上趕過去
No, she doesn't! I know what that is. You can stay.
不，不是的，我知道發生了什麼事 你可以留下來
I'll miss you too, Pheebs.
我也會想你的，菲比
And I will be holding you right here.
我會把你放在這裡
What movie do you wanna see? And not one I have to read.
你想看哪部電影？ 我不想看那種得認真看字幕的電影
I get that from books.
我受夠看書了
-Books? -Okay, car magazines, cereal boxes..
-書？ -好吧，汽車雜誌，玉米片包裝…
but it's enough!
但那就夠我受的了
Let's not see a movie. We'll just stay here and hang.
我們別去看電影 就待在家裡閒晃吧
-Just wait for Rachel to come back? -Hey, if that's what you wanna do.
-你要等瑞秋回來？ -如果你要那麼做的話
Dude, what is going on?
發生了什麼事？
-I have to find out how it went. -Why?
-我得知道他們之間怎麼了 -為什麼？
-He could be my baby's stepfather. -One date and they're getting married?
-他可能是我孩子的繼父 -才約會一次他們就要結婚了？
He's not you!
他不是你
I can't believe she's dating!
我不敢相信她去約會了
-What did you think she was gonna do? -I don't know.
-你覺得她該怎麼做呢？ -我不知道
-I can't believe this is happening. -What do you mean?
-我不會相信會發生這種事 -你是什麼意思？
I thought when I had another kid, it'd be different.
我以為我再生個孩子 情況會不一樣
I love Ben. But every time I drop him off at Carol and Susan's..
我愛班 但每次送他到卡蘿跟蘇珊家…
it breaks my heart a little.
我都會覺得很傷心
I've always had this picture of me and my next wife in bed..
我一直想像著 我跟未來的太太躺在床上…
my kid comes running in, leaps up on the bed and we all read the paper.
我的孩子跑過來跳到床上 我們會一起看報紙
Maybe fight over the science section.
或許還會搶著看科學版
-That's nice. You can still have that. -No. Rachel's out with some guy.
-那很棒，你還可以擁有那樣的夢想 -不，瑞秋跟別的男人約會
My baby went with her.
我的孩子跟她一起去了
If anything, that picture keeps moving further away.
如果出了任何事 那個夢想會離我越來越遠
Hey, can I ask you something?
我能問你一件事嗎？
In this picture of you and your wife, is your wife Rachel?
你想像你未來的太太時 她是瑞秋嗎？
It used to be.
以前是的
Now she doesn't really have a face.
現在我夢裡的人沒有臉
Smokin' body, though.
但她有很辣的身材
Good call. But the face, Ross, the face isn't Rachel.
說的好，但是羅斯 她已經不是瑞秋了
No. But how much easier would it be if it were?
對，但如果是的話 事情會變得很簡單吧？
That's not what she wants.
那不是她要的
I know. And I can't force myself to fall in love with her.
我知道 我不能逼自己愛上她
Ross, maybe you need a new picture.
羅斯，或許你需要新夢想
It won't be what you thought. But no matter what..
它會跟你之前的夢想不一樣 但不論如何…
there's gonna be a brand-new little baby. Your baby.
都會有個新寶寶 你的孩子
Who cares what the picture looks like?
誰在乎夢想是什麼樣的呢？
Yeah.
對
Let's you and me go out and have some fun.
我們一起出去 好好地玩一玩吧
Whatever you want. Come on.
你想做什麼都行，來吧
-We can catch that Ukrainian film. -No, I said fun.
-我們還趕得上看烏克蘭電影 -不，我說好玩的事
-Hey, Toby? -Hey, Bobby.
-嘿，托比 -嘿，巴比
It's Bob, actually.
事實上是巴伯
You work up here. Where's Chandler Bing's office?
你在這裡工作 錢德賓的辦公室在哪裡？
Yeah, it's right..
它就在…
Right there. Let me ask you, why?
就在那裡 你問這個做什麼？
I wanna talk to that bastard, see what his problem is.
我想跟那個混蛋談 看他有什麼問題
Okay, Bob. Listen.
好吧，巴伯，聽我說
I'm the reason you didn't get the job.
是我害你無法調職
-Toby, don't. -Bob.
-托比，不要 -巴伯
Toby, I'm not gonna let you cover for him.
托比，我不會讓你幫他說話
Anything you say will just get me more upset with Chandler.
你說任何話 只會讓我更氣錢德
That puts me in a difficult position.
那真的讓我很兩難
You do anything to Chandler, it's gonna bring you down to his level.
你生錢德的氣 只會讓自己跟他一樣卑鄙
I guess you're right.
我猜你說的對
Don't give him the satisfaction. You're better than Chandler. We all are.
別讓他得逞 你比錢德棒，我們都是
Especially me, Toby.
特別是我，托比
-Is everything okay? -That depends.
-沒事吧？ -那得視情況而定
-How are you and Phoebe? -Great. Thanks for introducing us.
-你跟菲比還好吧？ -很好，謝謝你介紹我們認識
My pleasure. Okay, I'm afraid I've got some bad news.
這是我的榮幸，好吧 我得跟你宣佈一個壞消息
-Phoebe! -Monica!
-菲比 -摩妮卡
-You're fired! -I'm breaking up with you!
-你被開除了 -我要跟你分手
I'm breaking up with you.
我要跟你分手
-You're fired. -Why?
-你被開除了 -為什麼？
I'm sorry. I'm not ready for a relationship right now.
抱歉 我還沒有準備好跟別人長期交往
I'm sorry too. But I like things done a certain way.
我也很抱歉 但我喜歡凡事照我的方法來做
-The chemistry's just not right. -The chemistry thing for us too.
-我們之間的化學反應不對 -我們也一樣
Wow. Okay.
好吧
I realize I came on a little strong. It's because I think you're amazing.
我知道我太黏了 那是因為我覺得你很棒
I wanna tell you how much I appreciate you giving me an opportunity.
我要告訴你 我很感激你給我機會
You're the most talented chef I've ever worked for.
你是我合作過 最有天份的廚師
Anyway..
總之…
-Tim, wait. -Yeah?
-提姆，等一下 -什麼事？
I spoke too quickly. There's a learning curve with this job.
我話說得太快了 這份工作需要時間學習
Maybe we could try it again.
或許我們能再試一次
Thank you so much. I know I can be better.
謝謝 我知道我可以表現的更好
And, Tim, I just want to say good luck here.
提姆 我只想說祝你好運
-Hello. -Hi.
-你好 -嗨
How was the date?
你約會情況如何？
I'm alone and I just bought $15 worth of candy bars. What do you think?
我一個人買了15塊錢的糖果 你覺得呢？
-What happened? -I told him I was pregnant.
-發生了什麼事？ -我告訴他我懷孕了
-He didn't take it so well? -Well, better than you.
-他不能接受？ -他的反應比你好
-But still not what you want. -Oh?
-但那仍不是你要的 -喔？
Yeah. He got all weird and sputtery. Then he said:
對，他真的是嚇壞了 然後他說
"I hear those hemorrhoids are a bitch."
「我聽說長痔瘡 真的很難過」
-He sounds swell. -Doesn't he?
-說的好 -是嗎？
You want a little cheering up? Sit down.
你要來點鼓勵嗎？坐下
Guess whose middle name is Muriel.
你猜誰中間名叫馬利歐
Chandler M. Bing. Oh, my God.
錢德·M·賓，天啊
-I'm sorry about your date. -It's all right.
-我很遺憾你的約會沒有成功 -沒事的
I guess I'm just done with the dating thing.
我猜我受夠了約會
Just one more thing in my life that's completely different.
那只是我生命中 另一件完全改變的事
-This is hard. -Yeah, I know.
-這真的很難 -我瞭解
On the other hand, in seven months you're gonna have something..
但反過來說 再過七個月你將能擁有一個孩子…
that you're gonna love more than any guy you've ever gone out with.
你對它的愛 勝過於你對其他人的感覺
Just wait.
等著吧
Wait until the first time your baby grabs your finger.
等到孩子第一次 抓住你的手指
You have no idea.
你不會瞭解的
Thanks, sweetie.
謝謝你，甜心
-You wanna grab some coffee? -No. I'm gonna go eat 10 candy bars.
-你要喝杯咖啡嗎？ -不，我要去吃掉10根棒棒糖
-I thought I cheered you up. -You did. There are 20 in here.
-我還以為我讓你心情變好了 -沒錯，我剛剛買了20根
-Good night. -Good night.
-晚安 -晚安
Ross? Hey, it's Mona. From the wedding.
羅斯，我是蒙娜 我們在婚禮上見過
-Oh, hi! -Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
-How are you? -I'm good, except you owe me a dance.
-你好嗎？ -我很好，但你欠我一隻舞
That's right. Well, would you be interested in seeing a Ukrainian film?
沒錯，你想看烏克蘭電影嗎？
Oh, you're serious. Sure.
你是認真的，好吧
Great. Well..
太棒了，喔…
-I think I need another cup of coffee. -Sure, let me get it for you.
-我想再來一杯咖啡 -沒問題，我去幫你拿
（謹以本片紀念 老理查寇克斯）
Bob?
巴伯
Bob!
-What the hell are you doing? -This is Chandler's office.
-你到底在做什麼？ -這是錢德的辦公室
Come on, Toby. Give me a hand!
來吧，托比，快來幫我